<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">It Was A Good Day</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="lyrics">Just wakin up in the mornin gotta thank God\n I dont know but today seems kinda odd\n No barkin from the dog, no smog\n And momma cooked a breakfast with no hog (damn)\n I got my grub on, but didnt pig out\n Finally got a call from a girl I wanna dig out\n (Whassup?) Hooked it up for later as I hit the door\n Thinkin will I live, another twenty-fo\n I gotta go cause I got me a drop top\n And if I hit the switch, I can make the ass drop\n Had to stop, at a red light\n Lookin in my mirror and not a jacker in sight\n And everything is alright\n I got a beep from Kim, and she can fuck all night\n Called up the homies and Im askin y all\n Which park, are y all playin basketball?\n Get me on the court and Im trouble\n Last week fucked around and got a triple double\n Freakin niggaz everyway like M.J.\n I cant believe, today was a good day (shit)\n \n Drove to the pad and hit the showers\n Didnt even get no static from the cowards\n Cause just yesterday them fools tried to blast me\n Saw the police and they rolled right past me\n No flexin, didnt even look in a niggas direction\n as I ran the intersection\n Went to Short Dogs house, they was watchin Yo! MTV Raps\n Whats the haps on the craps?\n Shake em up, shake em up, shake em up, shake em\n Roll em in a circle of niggaz and watch me break em\n with the seven, seven-eleven, seven-eleven\n Seven even back do Lil Joe\n I picked up the cash flow\n Then we played bones, and Im yellin domino\n Plus nobody I know got killed in South Central L.A.\n Today was a good day\n \n Left my niggas house paid (what)\ Picked up a girl been tryin to fuck since the 12th grade\n Its ironic, I had the brew she had the chronic\n The Lakers beat the Supersonics\n I felt on the big fat fanny\ Pulled out the jammy, and killed the punanny\n And my dick runs deep, so deep\n So deep put her ass to sleep\n Woke her up around one\n She didnt hesitate, to call Ice Cube the top gun\n Drove her to the pad and Im coastin\n Took another sip of the potion hit the three-wheel motion\n I was glad everything had worked out\n Dropped her ass off and then chirped out\n Today was like one of those fly dreams\n Didnt even see a berry flashin those high beams\n No helicopter looking for a murder\n Two in the mornin got the Fatburger\n Even saw the lights of the Goodyear Blimp\n And it read, Ice Cubes a pimp (yeah)\n Drunk as hell but no throwin up\n Half way home and my pager still blowin up\n Today I didnt even have to use my A.K.\n I got to say it was a good day (shit!)\n \n Hey wait, wait a minute Pooh, stop this shit\n What the fuck Im thinkin about?\n</string>
    <string name="image_description">Image of Ice Cube in a car</string>
    <string name="twitter">Twitter</string>
    <string name="meme">Meme</string>

</resources>
